you
so
much
for watching.
Off the Coast
of Laboratory 8
oh, oh, oh,
"Cruel Fate -
Kuma's Decision as a Father"
Cruel fate.
Kuma's decision as a father.
"Justice"
I'm here on business, I'm afraid.
It's awfully cold here.
Nothing like Punk Hazard at all.
Climate aside, this is where the future
of mankind itself will be created.
Honestly, dealing with the constant flow
of ideas is my biggest issue right now!
I can tell.
You've been too distracted to notice
some of the finer points of this lab.
I see what the issue is.
Not a word gets past us.
especially not any secret
deals with pirates.
Oh Stop it.
Don't you dare stop Borsalino.
You know I can't stand this side of you
It's not personal, friend.
I told you this is business
Is this Porcelino?
Yes, sir.
I'm in the lab now.
And you, Vega? Punk?
Are you listening?
I am.
Doctor.
I know our priorities are
different, but have some sense.
Kuma is strong. Of course.
He would make a fine base
for your clone soldiers.
But he is a pirate
wanted for $296 million.
A man like that cannot serve
as a symbol of justice.
Think of the Navy's reputation.
I don't care about saving face.
If the project succeeds, we'll be
saving lives, far more important.
That's true.
We can hardly ignore the
potential of such an endeavor,
assuming that you can see it to fruition.
And yet, I have terms.
Bartholomew Kuma,
if you're listening, my first demand is
that you join the seven warlords of the sea.
Recently,
a rookie named Ace took one of them down,
and we've been looking for a replacement.
The pirate world is in a state of chaos.
We need a man of your
caliber to rein it in.
Second,
in addition to the clones, you yourself
must become a human weapon for the Navy.
Are you saying I'd become a cyborg?
That's correct.
Then as a warlord, you could triumph
against any pirate in the world.
That'd make me safer, too.
You want that, don't you, friend?
Shut up, Kizaru!
I'm not finished.
Kuma, you also have history
with the Revolutionary Army.
Needless to say, that is a clear
conflict of interest for the government.
Which brings me to my third condition.
When the process ends, your mind
and free will will be erased.
I'm sad!
That is nothing but a
glorified death sentence!
Is this because the other
warlords won't obey?
A cyborg without free will
is a soulless robot! What?
You turn me into a murderer?
Is that what you want?
You are in no position to argue with me.
You are a Navy scientist.
Those are the conditions for saving
the life of a criminal's daughter.
If you do not accept,
then we will not spend a fortune on
surgeries to save some insignificant girl.
Hey, no running in the lab, please.
This is wrong. It's murder.
Performing such an
operation would be inhumane.
Vegapunk.
I want you to do it, Kuma.
I thought he was going to
make impossible demands.
I thought that I wouldn't
be able to save my daughter,
but I have nothing more to fear.
Thank you.
If you can help Bonney get well,
then I'll happily accept any fate.
Kuma.
Sentomaru, about the matter we discussed.
Huh?
One, two, one, two, three.
Little brat, come back!
Vegapunk, how long until Kuma is modified
and his daughter's treatment is complete?
The sapphire scale surgeries
will take six months and then
she'll have to wait another
year before she can go outside.
Kuma's modifications
should take two years.
I'm so happy.
This means body will be better
before her 10th birthday.
Your daughter will be our hostage.
Once she recovers, you will
have no reason to obey us.
You could take her and run.
I won't run, I swear!
We can't be too safe.
When her surgeries are complete,
we'll take custody of her.
As soon as your free will is gone,
then she will be allowed to leave.
And Kuma won't be able to see
her after she gets married!
That is correct.
Here is what will happen.
You'll perform Kuma's surgeries while
he serves as one of the seven warlords.
Once his daughter is cured, he will
be forbidden to contact her or escape.
If that rule is violated, she'll
be sent off to become a slave?
I'll never see her!
But I have just one request.
I don't want her to know the truth about
her disease or the fact
that she's a hostage.
So after her surgeries don't make
her stay at some government facility.
I Want you to let her
rest at the church in the
sorbet kingdom where she grew up
Nothing more, but right. I promise.
I'll never go there to see her.
I'll do exactly as you command.
Very well
It doesn't matter where she's under watch.
These next two years will be interesting.
Clank.
Hey, Dad!
Huh?
Bonnie!
Were you bored?
Sorry about that.
Hope you were a good girl. Always!
Uncle!
Huh?
Bonnie, we're staying here for
the next six months. We are?
Then you'll be here with me? Yep.
Turns out you're not the
only one who needs treatment.
I do, too.
Then we'll get better together!
Yay!
Dad, this weird guy is Saint Bonnie.
Wow, so polite.
I know she can be quite the handful.
Please be patient.
Yeah, fine. I'm grateful.
Hey, guess what?
This place is like a big maze
and it doesn't have any windows.
Wait, were you running around on your own?
It's dangerous here.
It's fine.
We're just a chicken. Stop!
Don't sneak off!
I have dreams to fulfill!
My hands can't keep up.
Someone must chronicle these endless!
Ideas for me?
Eat for me, go to the bathroom for me.
Oh, the violence!
It seizes me.
Can someone help me?
Even a cat would do.
If only there were five more of me?
Hey, Brook.
Sentomaru.
You holding up?
You busy? Let's play!
Come with me!
I have a job to do.
I know you're bored, but I don't have
time to hang out with you every day!
Well, maybe for a little while.
Slow down.
Oh, hey, Dad!
Hi there, Bonnie.
What kind of father are you?
Your daughter has no sense of modesty!
Isn't this fun?
We're playing horsey!
Your horse looks so friendly.
I mean, maybe you should let him
go back to the stable. Okie Dory.
I don't think she gets it.
Dad!
Huh?
What is it?
Wait, why do you have marks all over you?
Daddy!
Look, it's you!
It's perfect I'll treasure
this for the rest of my life
"Dad"
Thank you, Bonnie.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
I'm getting so hungry.
Is that...
Bonnie!
Hey, I was just about to come get you.
Perfect timing.
Are you ready for dinner?
AHHHHH!
We're all in!
Cheers!
Hey Dad, let's do the thing! Okay.
Doom da da da!
It's the Nita dance!
Come on, try it!
Ha-ha-ha!
Looks like fun!
How's this? That's it!
I don't have the Sanji for this!
Someone's a wallflower.
Uncle?
Fine.
I'll try it.
Six Months Later
All right, you're looking great.
One more year and you'll
be in perfect health.
Thank you for everything.
Thanks.
Um, once I get better,
can I come visit you?
Of course you can.
Hey, Dad.
Is the sea pretty?
Yes.
It's beautiful.
It's no fair. Don't worry.
You'll be able to see it soon.
You and me together.
Yeah.
I can't wait.
Sorbet Kingdom
Bonnie!
Kashi!
Welcome home!
It's been ages!
Are you going to live here again? Uh-huh!
My disease will be all gone in a year!
Then I can finally go outside!
My goodness!
That's wonderful!
You were sad you'd get better before you
were ten and it seems you were right!
Is someone in need of a babysitter again?
All bad Conney!
Queen Dowager Conney,
Sorbet Kingdom
We'd be happy to take
care of Kuma, don't worry.
Leave everything to us.
I'm grateful, you've all been too kind.
I'm a pirate now, so if I stick around,
it might cause trouble for everyone.
It'll likely be over a year
until I can come back? Really?
That's so long. How about
I write you letters?
When I pick you up, we'll take to the sea.
From there, it's an endless horizon!
Yeah, I can't wait.
I want to go all kinds
of places. That's great.
I'll take you anywhere you want to go.
If only that were true.
Don't worry.
She's in good hands.
Alpha, an Intelligence Agent
Cipher Pol No.8
Who is this woman?
Per the doctor's orders,
I'll be staying with Bonney until her
treatment's done and she's all better.
Every day I'll check her temperature,
give her medicine, and
monitor everything about her.
Nothing gets past me.
Hi, Bonnie!
I'm Nurse Alpha.
Hey!
What's that in front of the church?
That's where Bonnie will be staying.
But this hospital doesn't
allow any suspicious visitors,
so make sure you always carry your IDs.
That sounds annoying!
One toe out of line.
And I'll snap her little neck.
I know. I'll never come back.
Oh.
Goodbye Bonnie and thank you
thank you for being born.
Okay, I'm heading out.
Stay safe, okay?
and thus the tyrant became a warlord.
bartholomew kuma was obedient to his
orders from the world government.
"Seven Warlords of the Sea"
it made him a force to be reckoned
with for pirates across the world.
young master it says here
there's a new warlord?
Kuma the Tyrant, huh?
The seas are full of villains.
What's one more, I say?
Aren't you interested in the new warlord?
I don't give a damn who it is.
Now tell me, did you eliminate the
rat who saw our rainmaking ship?
Flawlessly.
They say he's as tall as Whitebeard. So
which one of us do you think is stronger,
Koby?
Oh, it's you, of course, Lady Alvida?
Jinbe! They found a replacement already!
Good luck, huh?
I don't want to hear that from you, Ace.
Don't joke!
This is your doing.
You're the one who beat Hina Buddha and
caused this mess in the first place.
So does the new guy meet
your lofty standards or not?
I'm trying to figure that out now.
The man's a former king?
That's a shock.
But I suppose he won't be the
only royalty in the group.
The world of pirates
certainly has changed.
This is of no concern to me.
I will not be going to
Central no matter what.
Such ignorance ill suits
the ruler of our land!
Get back here!
Ah, sissy!
It says he has paw pad powers.
Am I supposed to be scared of that?
Well, he wouldn't be a warlord
if he was weak, I suppose.
But the warlords work directly
under the government, right?
That's not the Kuma I know!
Dear Bonnie, I'm riding
you for my ship at sea.
"Dad"
I've become a bit infamous,
so it's harder to travel now.
But I'm doing fine.
Sorry, it's a bit far.
How's everyone?
I'll try to find all sorts of places that
you and I can visit once you turn ten.
Bartholomew Koala, you have a
new order from the government.
Where are you?
Oh, it's mad!
I'm in the East Blue.
What is the order?
Let's go.
I'll keep smiling.
I'll see you
next time.